<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- This file is part of the DITA Open Toolkit project hosted on 
     Sourceforge.net. See the accompanying license.txt file for 
     applicable licenses.-->
<!-- (C) Copyright IBM Corporation 2001, 2005. All Rights Reserved.
 *-->
<!DOCTYPE concept
  PUBLIC '-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN'
  'dtd1.2/technicalContent/dtd/concept.dtd'>

<concept id="sample_concept" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Desert Bus for Android</title>
  <shortdesc>The video game Desert Bus has been described as, "the most realistic verisimilitude
    reality game ever created."</shortdesc>
  <conbody>
    <p>Originally a minigame for the unreleased <i>Penn and Teller's Smoke and Mirrors</i> for the
      short-lived Sega CD, Desert Bus similates a bus' drive between Tucson, Arizona and Las Vegas,
      Nevada in real time. Players are awarded one point for completing the eight hour trip, during
      which time the maximum speed of the bus is 45 mph. At the completion of the trip, they are
      given several seconds to decide whether or not they would like to continue playing, attempting
      the trip back for an additional point. </p>
    <p>The game cannot be paused. If the bus veers off the road at any point, a tow truck will come
      to bring the vehicle back to the city of departure, also in real time, and then the game is
      over.</p>
    <p>When the original game developer went of business before the title was officially released to
      the public, the game was temporarily lost. However, in 2005, a promotional copy began being
      circulated on the world wide web, leading to Desert Bus gaining a cult following. </p>
    <p>Rights to the game were eventually purchased by the developer Amateur Pixels and a mobile
      version was released on all platforms. Today, the game costs $0.99 to download. All proceeds
      go to charity. </p>
    <p>It is widely agreed upon by experts that Desert Bus is the greatest video game ever created. </p>
  </conbody>
</concept>
